job-interview-site.com 2018-05-19

# Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email to info at job-interview-site.com .

At [http://www.job-interview-site.com](http://www.job-interview-site.com/) , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://www.job-interview-site.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, [http://www.job-interview-site.com](http://www.job-interview-site.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
[http://www.job-interview-site.com](http://www.job-interview-site.com/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [http://www.job-interview-site.com](http://www.job-interview-site.com/) .

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://www.job-interview-site.com and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

  * Google Adsense
  * Tribal Fusion
  * PulsePoint
  * Sovrn

**If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,[click here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/).**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://www.job-interview-site.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
[http://www.job-interview-site.com](http://www.job-interview-site.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://www.job-interview-site.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**Disable cookies**  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**How You Can Correct or Remove Information**  
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please Contact Us to: info at job-interview-site.com .

**Updates and Effective Date**  
[http://www.job-interview-site.com](http://www.job-interview-site.com/) reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on ou site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

**Agreeing to Terms**  
If you do not agree to [http://www.job-interview-site.com](http://www.job-interview-site.com/) ‘s [privacy policy](http://www.job-interview-site.com/privacy-policy) as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

## Limitation of Liability

Job-Interview-Site.com will not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages of any kind resulting from the use of or the inability to use Job-Interview-Site.com’s services, resulting from any goods or services purchased or obtained or messages received or transactions entered into through Job-Interview-Site.com’s services, resulting from loss of, unauthorized access to or alteration of a user’s transmissions or data or for the cost of procurement of substitute goods and services, including but not limited to damages for loss of profits, use, data or other intangibles, even if Job-Interview-Site.com had been advised of the possibility of such damages.  
In no event will Job-Interview-Site.com be liable for any:

  * Incidental, consequential or indirect damages (including, but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, business interruption, loss of programs or information, and the like) arising out of the use of or inability to use Job-Interview-Site.com, or any information, or transactions provided on ob-Interview-Site.com, or downloaded from Job-Interview-Site.com, or any delay of such information or service.  Even if Job-Interview-Site.com or its authorized representatives have been advised of the possibility of such damages, or;
  * Claim attributable to errors, omissions, or other inaccuracies in the service and/or materials or information downloaded through Job-Interview-Site.com.  Because some states do not allow the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, the above limitation may not apply to you.  In such states, Job-Interview-Site.com’s liability is limited to the greatest extent permitted by law.
